<electronics_unlabled>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:power_ups!_everything_you_need_to_know.:404knowmore
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
19 of 24
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Power UPS! Everything you need to know.
</title>
<date>
April 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
404knowmore
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First of all why do you want a power UPS? There are some very good reasons. (1) You never want your machine to go down incorrectly because of a blackout. (2) You want to work with clean power only. (3) You want to monitor your PC power. (4) You want to prevent your PC from being damaged due to a power problem like a lighting strike and want surge protection. The first rule about UPS is to never trust the insurance claim. Get your PC insured elsewhere. These companies have a tendency not to support their insurance claims. I have a PC running some very high specifications with over six USB devices, LCD monitor, printer and Ethernet equipment, with everything on at the same time. I have never gone above 325W of usage and average between 250W and 300W when managing a high spec game and doing lots of background tasks. Even though I have a 400W Power Supply Unit (PSU) I will be upgrading to a 500W PSU because it is better quality model. The way I can monitor how many Watts I use is with UPS software and hardware. So the question you need to ask is how many watts you will be using. The short answer to this is you don't know until you install the UPS and software that tells you how many watts you use because that appears to be the only way you can monitor your wattage at this time. You need to estimate what it is. I would say a high-end domestic PC (not a server) would use 300W max if it has one of every device you can think off turned on. As soon as we add things like another PC, or several printers, or several monitors, then we can start to overload a 325W UPS. This brings us to the first thing we need to learn about any UPS - Overloading and balancing. The overload feature is a warning system that turns on when you have overloaded the UPS capacity. Overloading does two things. It can in theory eventually damage the UPS and it voids the warranty. Most UPS are 325W but there are 800W - 1000W and even greater models out there for home networks that use more than one PC setup but to be honest you are probably going to get a UPS per PC setup rather than expensive bigger UPS for a network. So check the UPS rating. What UPS you choose depends on how much you want to load on it. Next thing you need to check with the UPS is if it comes with a USB connection. If it does this is a big plus because it means you can control it from your PC and the UPS comes with software. Now if the UPS has this feature then you can do loads of stuff like turning off UPS sound alarms, controlling how your UPS handles a blackout, how long it uses the battery before shutdown or hibernation, if it sounds an alarm or not, if it run self tests, data collection and monitoring, notifications and sensitivity settings. If the UPS does not come with a USB connection and software then you probably should be looking for an UPS designed for computer use rather than a UPS for non-computer equipment. Most UPS have LED indicators that tell you the status of the unit. The next thing to understand is that testing your UPS is not done by breaking it out of the box, connecting it to the mains, plugging your PC in and then turning off the house's power with the circuit breaker. You must charge the UPS first! So read the instructions. Usually you must attach the battery to the UPS (plug it in firmly!) and wait before using it. Then perform the test using the software first! Then you can consider trying to simulate a blackout in your home to see if the PC stays up. Usually a UPS is programmed to shutdown your PC if the blackout lasts for a few seconds. Nearly all UPS models with a USB connection can be customized for the shutdown event or how long the PC should hold for on the UPS battery. Most UPS devices allow you to connect a modem phone line into the device and then run a phone line into your modem. This is important because power surges on a UPS that do not have this protection can damage a PC through the unprotected phone line running into the modem that usually runs to the PC somehow. This is nasty problem with the degree of security that a UPS can provide. If it doesn't have this function then it is not going to provide 100% surge protection with a PC that is on-line. Networking a UPS PC to another PC without UPS can also increase the risk of surge protection problems. It is not recommend that you network a UPS PC to a non-UPS PC unless surge protection and the warranty are not an issue. One last thing is that some UPS have input regions on the UPS for surge protection and other input regions are not surge protected. Also with some models the batteries need to be replaced after a few years if you end up using them a lot. This is everything you need to know about an UPS before you choose one. It is basically now about downloading the technical specs of the UPS and making sure it provides you with what you need. The two top brands are APC and Belkin
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:good_product:s._reiss
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Good Product
</title>
<date>
January 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Reiss
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Annandale, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We bought this to backup the iMac G5 that I got my wife for Christmas. I have had an APC since 1996 and have depended on it to keep my systems running smoothly with the typical voltage fluctuations that we have in our area.

The overall product is very well designed and is a good value for the money.

I'm not sure if the Powerchute software was updated to run on Mac Tiger, howvever, so I did not install it.

Steve Reis
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:correction_to_earlier_review:j._zimmerlin_"jimzim"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
17 of 19
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Correction To Earlier Review
</title>
<date>
December 12, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Zimmerlin "JimZim"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Grover Beach, California USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It's unfortunate that an earlier review indicated that the unit had a serious flaw -- beeps whenever there is a problem with the incoming power.  This person obviously didn't take any time to familiarize himself with the software that controls the UPS.  The notification sounds can be completely turned off with the software.

I agree that I was annoyed when the unit made a loud beep in the middle of the night when there was a power problem.  Luckily, it was easy to turn this feature off.

Five stars for this product, for sure.

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:nedessary_accessory_for_all_computer_users:alan_brody_"al"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Nedessary accessory for all computer users
</title>
<date>
September 24, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Alan Brody "Al"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cincinnati, OH USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I replaced an older APC uninterruptible power supply with this one. I like the power bar design which makes it easy to use. It includes software to shut down your computer if the backup power gets low, and software so that you can choose not to get an alarm if the power goes out in the middle of the night. It has enough backup power to give my tower and monitor over 20 minutes of power if the wall power goes out. One tip; if you have a spare backup outlet, plug your electronic phone in. That way you won't be disconnected if there's a momentary power outage.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:don't_risk_being_without_one!:theresa_l._smith
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't risk being without one!
</title>
<date>
September 16, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Theresa L. Smith
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Blue Springs, MO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I already knew how good this product was before we bought it.  We had purchased one for my daughter and when lightening stuck it took out the surge protector and saved the computer.  I have recently learned I might have been able to have that replaced if I had thought to follow up.  But I was just so thrilled to have only lost an $80.00 (at that time) product and not a $1,200 computer.  When ordering mine, the price had come down quite a bit since we had first purchased one, I got free shipping, I never even had to leave the house!  I couldn't be happier!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUB:very_nice_source_of_backup_power_at_a_good_price:adnan_malik
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUB
</asin>
<product_name>
APC Back-UPS ES 500 Backup Battery and Surge Protector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Very nice source of backup power at a good price
</title>
<date>
September 14, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Adnan Malik
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cherry Hill, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Electricity in my apartment would randomly go out for a couple of seconds every few weeks, usually at night, but i would find that my servers had a harsh shutdown and rebooted the next day. Very frustrating and i would lose some unsaved work. This backup battery  takes care of that problem very well. It comes with windows client software that monitors the state of the battery and logs any power events. The software isnt of the best design but it works. No linux software but it can still be used without it. The unit has 6 power outlets but only 3 are powered by the battery. I have 2 servers and a router hooked up to it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:nice_rack:charles_m._miller
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
nice rack
</title>
<date>
August 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Charles M. Miller
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, TX United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It was easy to assemble and matches another one that I bought from the same company a few years ago
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:pros_and_cons:brandon_kurtz
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Pros and cons
</title>
<date>
January 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Brandon Kurtz
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Portland, OR USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have three of these CD towers, and in general I'm very pleased with them.  I like the wave design, and they hold a LOT of CDs.  I don't mind having to take off a whole stack of CDs to get to the one on the bottom, and as long as you balance the distribution of CDs properly, they don't tip that easily.  I always place mine next to a wall, anyway.  My biggest problem is that they are sometimes very difficult to put together.  Of course, that is only a temporary issue, although an incredibly vexing one. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:sturdy_with_form_and_function:griot_"chillib"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Sturdy with form and function
</title>
<date>
January 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Griot "chillib"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've had my Wave CD storage rack for almost 5 years now and I'm more than happy with it. It's been moved around, bumped and wedged between pieces of furniture, yet it has held on quiet nicely. I was originally attracted to it's wavey design which for me, is more artwork than just another storage case. I plan to buy another one
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:use_your_imagination_and_the_price_can't_be_beat:http://savegutenberg.blogspot.com
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Use your imagination and the price can't be beat
</title>
<date>
December 10, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
http://savegutenberg.blogspot.com
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This product is a great deal.  The problem with its shakiness can be easily solved with a little imagination.  Get two standard sized bricks and place them at the bottom of each of the two metal spires (they fit perfectly). Friends will compliment you on your post-modern taste and sense of design as well!  They will use up about 10 CD's worth of space but then you still have storage for about 100 standard cd-cases or 200 thin ones.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:does_the_job_while_looking_good!!:mr.blb
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
does the job while looking good!!
</title>
<date>
April 18, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Mr.BLB
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CT
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
as someone else mentioned its not the sturdiest rack out there, but it has not tipped over on me so i really cant complain.
it looks good, and its easily put together. 

as for the sturdy issue, i look at it like this. since when do you place cd racks in the middle of the room?? NEVER!! 
people will typically place them in the corner of a room which is fine and you will NEVER have an issue with the rack at all. i have mine set right near the entrance of the bedroom door and i have brushed up against it and bumped elbows with it, and it ever so slightly moved a little but nothing where i was worried about it falling. oh and i have carpet in my room which makes it for a less sturdy foundation. 
i have even thought about purchasing another one for dvd's.

personally speaking i def recommmend this cd rack
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005UKBG:it_does_the_job:diane_m._chalmers
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005UKBG
</asin>
<product_name>
Atlantic 1316 CD Storage Case (110-Capacity, Wave): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
It does the job
</title>
<date>
November 25, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Diane M. Chalmers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Wisconsin USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have never had this device fall over like others have complained of, either.  Granted, I do have mine situated one a hard wood floor but even so - it seems sturdy enough.

It is a little irritating with the wave structure how some of CDs won't fit but other than that I find this tower really helpful.  It's a nice and fun way to store your CDs
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:just_amazing_!!!!!____:ernest_o._kanu_"ernest"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Just Amazing !!!!!    
</title>
<date>
June 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ernest O. Kanu "Ernest"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Yakima, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The first time I saw this piece was at Wal-mart. I had listened to Sony,Philips, JVC, Panasonic, RCA in that order, the difference was instantly clear. Then I went back to listen to the Philips again and the difference was clear.I recommend that first time buyers should go to a store with several brands on display that they could listen to. I made up my mind that if  I wanted a home theater in a box (HTIB)package it will be the Philips brand.This was about 10 months ago. Each time I stopped by the electronic section of any store I would check it out. Finally, I decided to buy one. Next thing was to read expert reviews and consumer reviews. Most reviews rated it high. However, I was concerned about the hissing sound some consumers had experienced.I still went ahead to buy one at Fred Meyer for $179:00 on sale, if I did not like it, I will return it, I reasoned. I bought the black colored piece. Costco and Radioshack had it on sale for the same price but Fred Meyer is closer to my home. 
Since adding this piece to our family room, the audio effects in our family room is certainly more welcoming, warmer , richer and entertaining than before.
 I will address the concerns of a few reviews here.
1. Hissing sound: I found none, but discovered that if the audio OUT on your TV has one jacket like mine, instead of two or three jackets, then you need to get an extension RCA jacket that will split your one outlet to two or three OUT jackets with the apporpriate color codes (white, red (for two jackets) and yellow for the third jacket) to match the audio IN jacket (white and red) of the DVD player, otherwise you will get either a humming or hissing sound. Please note that the key here is to have the color codes on your TV audio OUT,to match the color codes on your Philips DVD  audio IN otherwise you will get a humming or hissing sound.

2. DVD player jumping disc: You are using a defective disc. solution: change your disc.

3. Back speakers not working: They will not work if you do not use the remote control to adjust the surround and sound buttons to the appropriate mode e.g. movie , stereo etc. Sometimes, some movies are not recorded to produce surround sound effect, so change the TV channel or your DVD disc.

4. Speaker wires not long enough:Some consumers had enough length, mine were too short for our large family room (too large for me to bother to measure). One reviewer was able to use banana plugs to make the adaptation,I could not. So I returned the banana plugs, I bought from Home depot. Instead, I  bought some digital extension cables. They come in different sizes 14G,16G,18G,20G etc. The smaller the size number, the thicker the cable, the better, to avoid loss of digital signals. I bought size 14G. The risk with attaching extension cables is that since you will have to cut into the original cables that come with the equipment you can not return your equipment to the store nor sell it at ebay for a good price if you wanted to,since it will be considered tampered with. But be reassured you will not need to dispose of this equipment once you have it properly set up.If you decide to use additional extension cable/wire, cut the orginal wire at about 6 inches from the speakers. Attach your extention cable to this cut end and run the attached extension cable from your speaker location to where your equipment is.Then attach the other end of your extension cable to the other end of the original cable, so you can still use the proprietary speaker plugs that came with your equipment to attach to the back of the set.This method makes it cosmetically suitable to have one cable (i.e. the extension) run through your entire room and at the same time use the the proprietary plugs attached to the orginal cable at the other end with your equipment, which by the way is the only plug that fits into the jackets at the back of the DVD player/receiver.REMEMBER to tape over all exposed wires/cables with nonconductive electric tape. Normally, comes in black.
Caution: you need to buy enough length of extension cable though, they come in 25ft, 50ft and 100ft length. Having a large room I bought three 50 feet cables to do the job satisfactorily.The cost for each 50 ft cable was $19:00.



5. Wall mountings:The enclosed wall mountings are fixed. You can not rotate the position of your speakers once mounted. For less than $15:00 at Wal-mart , I bought a set of 5 speakers wall mounts that I can rotate from side to side or move up and down to a suitable head angle.

Speaking of the sound production, it is clear, crisp and true theater realism. The sonics can not be described justily unless you hear it for your self.Do your self a favor and buy one.

But for the proprietary plugs that make it difficult to consider using extension cables , I would have given it 5 stars. Philips should make the plugs universally adaptable, so consumers wil not have second thoughts about adding extension cables, if they needed to. Better still, Philips could add more length to the cables or make provisions for one to order fitting extension cables through them so you do not have to cut into the original cables. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:great_system:trevor_s._hurlington
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great System
</title>
<date>
April 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Trevor S. Hurlington
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
 I was blown away by the sound quality. Good system at a reasonable price. I would recommend this system to all my friend
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:great_product:a._manezes
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Product
</title>
<date>
March 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Manezes
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Mateo, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had read some other reviews stating that this Home Theater System makes a buzzing noise.  However, I had my doubts so I ordered it anyway and it's great.  No buzzing noise on mine at all.  I have an apartment and didn't really want to spend a whole lot of coin on a major system that I couldn't really use anyway because of noise restrictions.  This system is nice and clear and gives me the Home Theater Experience I was looking for.  They give you plenty of wire to run along the edge of a room and still have enough slack to hang the rear speakers up behind the couch on the wall.  Granted the speaker wire isn't all that thick, and has a proprietary male/female connector into the unit which would make upgrading to monster cable a pain.  It still sounds great and for under $200 bucks why would you care anyway. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:hissing_is_a_bad_thing:shadoxfire
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Hissing is a Bad Thing
</title>
<date>
March 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Shadoxfire
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pacific Northwest USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We own the HTS3400 bought at Costco.  It is possible that the newer "D" model has fixed the hissing we hear during stand-by mode.  We have owned it about a year now and I believe it is getting louder.  When the house is quiet I can hear it in the next room.  It doesn't bother my wife; she finds it restful.  I don't like it because I don't think it should be making any sound at all.  Given the choice I would NOT buy this product again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:great_player_at_a_reasonable_price:praveen_kumar_"praveen"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great player at a reasonable price
</title>
<date>
March 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Praveen Kumar "Praveen"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Plano, TX
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
A very good player at a very reasonable price. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:wow:b._hawkins_"willie"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Wow
</title>
<date>
March 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Hawkins "Willie"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Eastern CT
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is prob. the best item I`ve boughten this year..!!!
Totaly awsome system TV, Radio, Surround all in one..!
Great buy.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:awesome_value!!_highly_recommend!:s._tucker_"dance_freak"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Awesome Value!! Highly Recommend!
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Tucker "dance freak"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this system recently after my Panasonic DVD Surround System broke. I was a little leary about this system since other reviewers have mentioned a hissing noise here on Amazon and other sites for that matter. But I couldn't find anything like this value and decided I could just take it back if I didn't like it. Well, I love it! The sound is great! Subwoofer is awesome! I do not hear a hissing noise at all. This sounds so much better than my Panasonic which broke and that I had paid $100 more for
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:nice_but_noisy:stv_damazon
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
nice but noisy
</title>
<date>
February 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
stv damazon
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
seattle, wa
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Costco here too. 180 was a great price, but the hissing has become annoying. It does sound like a larger capacitor....its constant...constant. i hear it walking through the room passing within 8-10 feet of the unit. the noise dissapears when tray is open, only. i really like it, but the hiss is getting to me. I notice its on sale here for $129. Maybe ill shop around, spend a bit more
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:fast_delivery_but_some_broken_tabs:betsy_sickbert
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Fast delivery but some broken tabs
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Betsy Sickbert
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
SANTA CLAUS, IN United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
packaging by mfg doesn't keep tabs from being broken off, but vendor was great
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:these_jewel_cases_are_fine:leonard_kocurek
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
These Jewel Cases are fine
</title>
<date>
October 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Leonard Kocurek
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These clear jewel cases make it easy to see what you have and the slim design saves space.  I use them for cd's and dvd's.  I haven't had any problems with them; they are a good value
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:very_good:irina_camp_"wwe_is_the_best_of_the_best!"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
very good
</title>
<date>
September 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Irina Camp "WWE is the best of the best!"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fairfax Station, VA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
these are very good for dvd or cd storage. very inexpensive and very good quality. people who complain below have fat fingers, thats why they break the cases
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:joe_barone_big_buyer:joseph_barone
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Joe Barone Big Buyer
</title>
<date>
August 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joseph Barone
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NEW YORK USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
cases very cheaply made. Break when opening. Not worth shipping cost waste of money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:they're_ok:nhopps
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
They're OK
</title>
<date>
February 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
nhopps
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Hinton, WV United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just a note to those who've been having trouble opening these cases, without breaking them. If you use an emory board to slightly sand the top knob which is holding the case together, you'll be able to open and close it ok. Don't sand too much, and just do the top knob, or it won't hold together. I like the fact that these cases are clear and fairly inexpensive, so I wanted to make them work. Hope it works for you
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:too_hard_to_open:nsc
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Too hard to open
</title>
<date>
January 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
NSC
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It is difficult not to break them when first trying to open them.  On the flip side once they have been opened once, they don't reclose very well
</review_text>
</review>
</electronics_unlabled>